Previously on Teen Wolf...
Even if you don't trust me,
I'm still going to be
looking out for you...
Scott. Promise me
you'll do everything you can to save her.
I promise.
They're here.
She's getting worse. If she's a
real werewolf, we can save her.
You gotta give her the bite.
No.
What do you mean, "No"?
Liam, look at her.
She's too weak. It will kill her.
We don't even know what
the mercury's doing to her.
We don't even know if
it is actually mercury.
This can't be the only
way to save her life.
It saved mine.
You know, that was different.
You were hanging off a ledge.
You promised.
You said you'd do everything you could.
Which is why I'm not going to do
something I think is going to kill her.
There has to be...
There has to...
Scott.
There's another way to save her.
Guys, I
don't know what the statistics are
for surviving a werewolf bite,
but she's definitely not surviving this.
We need to do something.
No.
Unit 7, can you 10-9?
I didn't quite get that.
10-4, Dispatch,
I'm southbound on Fryman
following suspicious individual
loping in the middle of the road.
7, clarify loping.
Uh... Running on all fours.
Suspect is possibly a large animal.
Unit 5 to Dispatch,
I'm turning the corner on Lincoln.
Suspect no longer loping but running.
10-4. Unit 5, clarify running.
Two legs. Moving fast.
Copy, what's your speed?
45 to 50.
Advise that suspect is
too large to be human.
10-4, Unit 5, back off and maintain eyes.
Dispatch to all units,
be on the lookout for
suspicious bipedal animal.
Unit 8 to Dispatch,
advise coming up on Taft,
animal is back on all fours and...
Holy...
Unit 8, it's Stilinski. Report.
10-4, Sheriff.
Suspect just leapt over my car.
Dispatch, I have
eyes on the suspect.
Corner of Union, heading north
towards Beacon Hills High School.
Confirm back on all fours.
Uh, 10-4, can you give its 20?
In my rear view mirror.
Coming right toward
me. Advise suspect is...
Oh, my God.
Clark, back off...
All available units
to Beacon Hills High School.
Proceed with caution.
Clark!
I'm here!
Sheriff, my car... It's wrecked.
I'm sorry, it's probably totaled.
I ran half a mile to get here,
trying to follow the... The thing.
Hey, hey, hey... Forget about the car.
Insurance will cover it.
Yeah, well...
I wonder how much insurance the school has.
Success?
Imminent.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com
Okay.
What's that?
It's called chelation therapy.
It removes heavy metals from the blood.
But, the problem is, is
that can injure the kidneys
and Hayden only has
one to begin with, so...
Hey, you're hurting her.
And you're hurting me.
- Sorry.
- Hey, guys...
Remember, we're here to save a life.
Not kill each other.
It's the full moon.
We can feel it even during the day.
And it's a Supermoon.
What is that supposed to make
you guys, like super strong?
Super aggressive?
Both.
You know we're going to need help with him.
He'll be all right.
He's 16 and in love.
First love. You remember what that's like?
Yeah, trust me, I remember.
All those emotions
mixed with the Supermoon.
Tonight isn't going to be good.
I know.
We need help,
and I don't mean restraints or chains.
I mean Malia, Stiles, Lydia.
You need your pack, Scott.
I'm not so sure I have one anymore.
Let me talk to them.
Let me see what I can do. Okay?
Theo.
Thank you.
Go home, Lydia.
Stilinski isn't telling
anyone where he put the bodies,
and I'm pretty sure I'm not psychic.
But you're drawn to death.
Just like me.
Does that make me a kind of Banshee?
You find bodies.
I find Chimeras.
Dead Chimeras.
So, we're both harbingers of death.
I should probably add that to my resume.
Hmm.
It's on my college applications.
Can they fix it?
There's not enough duct tape
in the world to fix that thing.
Maybe you should try
something other than duct tape.
It's got a bad alternator,
you know, needs all new belts,
transmission's going...
The brake pads are
basically metal on metal.
How come you let it get so bad?
There's been a few distractions,
if you haven't noticed.
I notice.
More than you think I do.
Uh, I didn't mean it like that.
Am I taking you home?
No. Sheriff station.
I gotta talk to my dad.
Does it help knowing?
Knowing what you are?
It doesn't scare me as much.
That I know.
Do I scare you?
Once.
Really?
It was the night I found that werewolf,
the one with the talons.
I thought I was going to die that night.
How come?
Because I saw you.
I saw the Banshee.
But I guess it was just a
dream or a hallucination.
What was I doing?
Trying to keep me alive.
Well, sorry, but the Banshee was
mostly trying to stay out the rain.
That was the night of the storm, remember?
The Wild Hunt.
The what?
Oh, it's something Kira was telling me.
A myth about thunderstorms...
Ghost Riders in the sky and black dogs...
What is it?
I need to check on something.
I'll be right back. Don't go anywhere.
You know what I mean.
It's not working, is it?
She should be showing signs of improvement.
Hayden?
Call Val...
My sister... Valerie.
She's a deputy.
I think I might know where she is.
Theo just texted me about the high school.
He said there's cops everywhere.
Might be another Chimera.
Um, my sister...
I don't want to die without my sister.
I'll get her.
Uh, wait. What are you going to tell her?
If I have to, I'll tell her everything.
You want me to go in with you?
No, it's okay. It's probably
going to take a while.
Are you going to tell him about Donovan?
You knew?
I guessed.
I saw the bite on your shoulder
while you were sleeping.
It didn't matter to me.
That's why I never said anything.
It matters to me.
Sheriff left half an hour ago.
He said he was on his way back.
Okay, thanks. I'll just wait in his office.
"Woden's Hunt,
"also known as the Wild Ride or Wild Hunt.
"A myth of devilish riders in the sky
"accompanied by black dogs,
"spectral beasts whose
eyes glowed with fire,
"A Bearer of Death
"and Guardian of the Supernatural,
"the black dog is also known
"by its more common name...
"The Hellhound."
You know what's coming.
Don't you?
Someone's going to die here.
You're right.
But I can't let you tell anyone.
Why?
Because I want you, Lydia.
I want all of you.
What are you talking about?
Don't worry.
I'll give you some time to think about it.
How did you do that?
It's on her neck too.
She's getting worse, isn't she?
Yeah. Which is why we're
taking her to the hospital.
How's that going to help?
We're in an animal clinic and I
need equipment designed for humans.
I said that we're going to
take her to the hospital.
I didn't say we're going
through the front door.
Hey, what's going on?
Somebody hit the fire alarm?
Do you want to learn?
I can show you.
You're showing me plenty right now.
I've got nothing to hide.
And I do?
Did you tell Scott you're
planning to kill your mother?
Don't worry, I'm not judging.
I want to help you. Why?
Because I know Scott won't.
I'm trying to help all of you.
If Scott can't do it, then someone
else needs to take the lead.
You know they're moving
Hayden to the hospital, right?
But Hayden's still a Chimera,
and there's two more we haven't found yet,
and they're still dangerous.
They need help.
They need you.
What the hell...
Wait, wait, wait...
Don't shoot! Don't shoot!
Get back! Stay out of his way.
What's happening?
I'm not sure.
But it's definitely not good.
My sister...
Scott's out looking for her right now.
He's going to bring her here
as soon as he can, all right?
Hey, Lydia?
That's not possible.
You're right.
A werewolf shouldn't even be
able to touch mountain ash.
You're a Chimera.
I'm the first Chimera.
It's the coyote part you don't notice.
It's why Malia trusted me first,
even though she probably didn't know it.
You found the perfect word though, Scott.
Because a Chimera isn't just
a monster with different parts.
It can also mean something
impossible to achieve.
An unrealizable dream.
And they realized you?
They came close with me.
But we can't all be perfect.
We can't all be true Alphas.
Damn. I felt that.
No calls, Scott.
No Stiles, no Malia, no Lydia.
You're just going to have to wait
here alone for what happens next.
What do you mean?
What's next?
The Supermoon.
Over here, yeah.
Shouldn't we be talking
to one of the doctors?
I've been wrestling with that for hours.
Do we bring them in
and watch them treat
her as a normal patient,
while we stand here knowing
that's not going to work?
Or do we keep trying everything
medically possible to save her,
while her body does things that
shouldn't be medically possible?
Is she dying?
With the amount of mercury
in her body right now,
she shouldn't even be alive.
Come on...
You've done this before.
You can do it again.
Wolfsbane.
Theo let you in.
Did you lie to me?
I've never lied to you.
But you won't save her.
I can't save her.
At least, not with a bite.
If you'd just think about
that for a second, Liam,
you would know that I'm right.
I am thinking!
I'm thinking about alternatives.
Liam, it's the Supermoon.
It's feeding your anger. It's
making you more aggressive.
It's making me stronger!
You're gonna keep your promise.
Even if it kills you!
Oh, no, no, no, no...
I think you better get Liam.
What about Scott? He's not answering.
And if Liam wants to be with
her, he needs to get here now.
Because she's dying,
and I don't know what else to do.
Go. I will text you if anything changes.
Just get him here, Mason.
Go.
Hey, Liam, stop.
You're not going to save her by killing me
What the hell was that?
I don't know what's going on around here,
but I'm guessing things are bad again.
Very.
Then this is going to sound worse.
'Cause your plan...
She knows. Yeah.
And she's coming.
The Desert Wolf knows you're alive.
And she's coming back to Beacon Hills.
Come on, come on...
Sorry. I got here as fast as I could...
We gotta go. Now. Parrish
has got the bodies.
Okay, wait up... Stiles, wait.
Parrish is out and he's got the bodies.
We've got to find Scott.
And we've got to tell him.
Stiles!
I don't think Scott wants
to talk to you right now.
Yeah, thanks, I'm aware of that.
It doesn't matter. He
needs to know about this.
Stiles...
Scott doesn't want to talk to you.
But I think your dad does.
Don't do this, Liam!
I can't let you kill me.
Your dad was looking for you, Stiles.
He found me instead.
Where is he?
I covered for you.
This was taken care of.
If Melissa didn't find
it at the hospital...
Guess even the son of
a cop can make mistakes.
Did you hurt him?
I never lied about why
I came to Beacon Hills.
I'm here for a pack.
I came for the werecoyote.
The one whose first instinct is to kill.
I came for the Banshee, the
girl surrounded by death.
I came for the dark Kitsune,
the Beta with anger issues...
I came for Void Stiles.
That's the pack I want.
Unfortunately, it doesn't include Scott.
Your heartbeat's rising, Stiles.
It's not because you're afraid.
Nogitsune is gone,
but you've still got more blood
on your hands than any of us.
I'm about to get more.
I'll tell you where your dad is,
if you promise not to help Scott.
There he is!
That's Void Stiles.
It felt good, didn't it?
We won't tell Scott.
'Cause you can't lose
your best friend, right?
Even though we both know,
you never needed him.
You hate me now, but
you'll get it eventually.
This is the hard part.
'Cause you can't help Scott
and save your dad's life.
You've still got time, Stiles.
You've still got time.
He's using you, Liam.
He wants you to be the Alpha
because he can't take the power from me.
Only you can.
But once you do,
he'll take it from you.
That's why he wants you to kill me...
That's what you don't get, Scott.
I want to kill you.
I want to!
Liam!
Liam, what are you doing?
Hayden.
She's gone.
Hayden died a few minutes ago.
Scott...
What happened?
It's the Supermoon.
- It was just...
- Bad timing.
I mean, seriously. You couldn't
have waited five minutes?
I should've stayed.
I should've made sure.
Because now you have to kill me yourself.
They're still mine.
Maybe not yet, but they'll come around.
Not for you.
They're not like you.
They never will be.
Because I'm a Chimera?
Because I'm not a real werewolf?
Because you're barely even human.
Scott! Scott!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Okay.
What...
One, two, three, four,
five... What are you doing?
Six, seven, eight...
What are you doing?
Bringing him back.
But his... His heart. He...
He hasn't had a pulse in over 15 minutes.
You can't bring someone back that's...
He's not someone. He's my son.
And he's an Alpha.
And he's too strong to die like this!
Come on!
Open your eyes and look at me, okay?
Come on. Breathe, baby. Breathe.
Melissa, it's... Shut up!
He's too strong to die like this.
Come on. You can do this. You're an Alpha.
You're an Alpha.
Come on, Scott. Roar.
Come on!
Come on, Scott. Roar!
I've never done this before, Lydia.
I know how dangerous it is.
But it's a risk we have
to take. No, no, don't!
What do you think, Lydia?
Am I doing it right?
Yes, I see it...
I can see it.
I lost, Mom.
Every leader suffers loss.
Sometimes more than you think is bearable.
But this time, I lost everyone.
You'll get them back.
You have to.
Why would they come back?
Because you're their leader.
And even when a leader thinks
they have nothing left to give,
there's still one thing.
Hope.
Give them hope.
Come on, Lydia.
Come on.
Watch this, Lydia.
You think you lost your mind?
Well, watch this!
What... What's happening?
Who are you?
I'm your Alpha.
And all of you...
All of you belong to me.
La Bete.
La Bete...
Success.
Sync & corrections by wilson0804
www.Addic7ed.com