Previously on "The Whispers"...
- My head kind of hurts.
- Minx?
As Drill is becoming
weaker, our kids are, too.
Isolate them?
Drill said we'll all get better
as soon as he finds Orion.
"Orion" could mean a person or a place.
Someone with access who could
help him send the signal.
Is someone there?
Stay away!
It's a burn mark. Drill is here.
He's possessed one of the children.
It could be any of them.
Silas, do you know who Drill is?
It's Drill! I told you he'd know!
Daddy! Daddy!
It's okay, Minx.
It's all right. Daddy's here.
Okay, come here. It's okay.
It's okay. I got you. All right.
All right.
You okay?
Huh, what's wrong?
I had a bad dream.
Well, you're awake now.
I don't like being scared.
I know. I know.
But, you know, when I was little,
I was afraid of the dark.
- You were?
- I was.
But grandpop, he...He taught me something.
You know that... you know
that song, "twinkle twinkle"?
You remember?
Well, it used to be a poem.
And he said that when I felt scared,
I should say the poem out loud,
because it worked like magic and
all my fears would disappear.
I want to learn it.
Are you sure? It's very powerful magic.
Okay. Well, repeat after me.
Twinkle, twinkle.
Little star.
How I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high...
like a diamond in the sky.
Like a diamond in the sky.
When the blazing sun is gone.
When he nothing shines upon.
Then you shine your little light.
Twinkle, twinkle in the night.
Then the traveler in the dark...
thanks you for your little spark.
He could not see which way to go...
If you did not twinkle so.
I am telling you, there is no way that
Minx would have let this happen, sir.
Wes, over 50 people saw her
burn the president's daughter.
I'm very... I'm very
aware of the situation.
It's the same burn mark
that was found on
Dr. Benavidez, Thomas Harcourt.
How do you explain that?
I don't know, but I... I know there's
another explanation for this.
Yeah, one of these kids is inhabited...
not my daughter!
Let me talk to her. I'll...
Do you really think
you're an impartial judge?
Claire.
- Please. Please.
- Wes, I can't.
- I can't do... I can't be the one.
- Okay, just... just go...
just go and ask her
what really happened, okay?
Please.
You're the only one I trust.
You can leave.
Minx, I need to talk to you.
If I can understand
what happened out there,
what happened to Cassandra, I can help you.
You want me to prove I'm not Drill.
Can you?
Well, if I was Drill,
wouldn't I want to trick you
into thinking I'm not?
So...
no matter what I do...
Besides...
why do I have to prove it?
Shouldn't you have to prove I'm guilty?
Why don't we try something?
I'm gonna take your gloves off.
- You want me to touch you?
- Like you did Cassandra, yes.
But...
Aren't you scared?
I'm trying not to be.
I don't want to do this.
Okay.
Okay. One more thing.
Can you tell me what Orion is?
I don't know...
you say you want to help me,
- but you keep asking me questions.
- I do want to help you.
I do want to help you, Minx.
No, I don't believe you.
Why would you say that?
'Cause you don't like me.
- No, that is... that's not true.
- You want me to be guilty.
No.
You want me to be Drill.
'Cause then you get everything...
Don't you?
All I want right now...
is to find Drill.
Do you really think
it's gonna be that easy?
Synced and corrected by oykubuyuk
www.addic7ed.com
So, Dr. Benavidez told you about Drill?
Not exactly.
See, she was frightened...
couldn't give me the full story.
That's how it usually works
with whistle-blowers.
They give you a bread crumb
and hope you find the truth
and leave them out of it.
- What's the bread crumb?
- Harbor Point.
She told me to dig into the real story.
That's when I learned about the meltdown,
what happened afterwards,
and how Drill was responsible.
So you know what Drill is.
As far as I can tell,
it's a secret government
nuclear-testing program.
Now, whether Drill is
an acronym or a code name...
I'm still working on that one.
But that night, at Harbor Point,
something went wrong,
and children in the surrounding
area started getting sick,
including your son.
So in order to contain the situation
and keep the truth from getting out,
our government issued a round-up.
Now 87 children are locked up
with no hope of ever getting out.
I just need confirmation.
I think we're done here.
Just give me something.
The public, they have a right
to know what's really happening.
You think you're gonna be
able to hide this much longer?
Other news outlets, they're
already chasing the story.
Please.
Wait.
He's right.
It's just a matter of time.
How about we make a deal?
You help me get what I want,
I'll give you the
biggest story of your life.
Henry.
I need to ask you something.
It's about Minx, isn't it?
You were right there.
You saw what happened.
I don't want to get Minx in trouble.
Neither do I.
But right now, we really
need to know the truth.
She...
She grabbed Cassandra.
And you're sure about this?
'Cause, Henry, I need you to be
100% sure that it was Minx.
Silas, walk us through that night...
the night that you saw
Dr. Benavidez get killed.
Can you do that?
Okay.
What were you doing out here
so late at night?
I had to go to the bathroom...
but I got lost.
There was a light from one of the offices.
She was talking on the phone... the doctor.
What was she saying? Do you remember?
I don't remember the words,
but she sounded worried.
It doesn't make any sense.
She saw something bad
on the computer, I think.
Then what happened?
There was a sound. It came from there.
Someone was there, but I couldn't see who.
So the doctor,
I think she saw who was there,
who was at the door, and...
Silas, it's okay.
It's okay.
There was this funny noise, like... A zap.
No. No.
Stay away!
The doctor... she fell down.
She stopped moving.
And you saw who it was, didn't you?
She didn't see me at first.
I tried to get away.
Then she saw me.
She said she was going to kill my mom.
She said if I told anyone...
- Is my mom okay?
- Yes.
Yes.
She's okay.
I need to know if you're sure...
It was Minx that you saw.
It was her. I swear.
We have something.
We were able to recover
partial fragments
of Dr. Benavidez's hard drive.
Here's the activity log from that night.
At 11:06 P.M., she made an
entry into a notes field.
At the same time,
she was talking to an unidentified number.
- No trace yet of who she was talking to?
- Not yet, sir.
But at 11:09 P.M.,
her call was disconnected.
The next activity... 12:28 A.M.
That's after her time of death.
Someone accessed that same file,
somehow bypassing her security password.
They then erased
the last note that was made.
Any way to recover the note?
Unfortunately not.
But I was able to determine
which file was modified.
Millicent?
That's Minx's real name.
Drill was covering his tracks.
The doctor must have found
some kind of evidence
that proved Minx is Drill.
That'll be all for now.
I believe I have what I need now.
But since Wes has asked for
your input, Agent Bennigan...
What's your professional opinion?
Wes...
It isn't just the burn mark.
Silas... he knew details
that he could have only known
if he was actually there,
and you heard his voice...
a child his age can't
fake that kind of fear.
Okay, so he saw something...
We both know that witnesses...
and Minx's file, if something was erased...
We don't know... We don't know
what was in that file, Claire.
All I can do...
is look at this like you and I
have been trained to do.
I wish... I wish...
more than anything that I could conclude
- something else.
- Claire. Claire. Claire.
Please.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
Thank you, Agent Bennigan.
- What are you doing?
- Jessup, he's right.
The truth is gonna come out...
maybe not today, but soon.
Let's make this work for us.
Us?
And how exactly does that work?
Reporters have to fact-check, right?
Meaning?
Meaning I tell him everything
that's really going on
with the kids, with Drill.
His first call's gonna be to
the White House
for confirmation.
After that...
Pressure's on.
They're gonna have to release the kids,
or they're gonna have to deal
with the backlash of the public.
You mean panic.
'Cause that's what
we're talking about here.
It's only a matter of time.
Time is something that I do not have.
I want my son home now.
- I want those removed.
- I'm sorry, sir.
I have my orders. This is ridiculous!
She is a child!
Come on.
Sir! Sir!
No, stop!
I'll have no choice but to escort you out.
Do you understand?
Yes.
10 minutes.
That's what you've been cleared for.
Hey.
You okay, sweetie?
You have to get me out, daddy.
Honey, I just need
a little more time, okay?
- How much time?
- All right?
I know they're gonna do something to me.
Sweetie, I will not let them hurt you.
I promise, okay?
All right?
I'm scared.
I know.
But you and I... we just need
to be brave right now, okay?
Okay, baby. It's all right.
Alright?
Hey. I understand.
It's okay.
Hey.
Do you remember, uh...
You remember when... When you were little
and we used to... We used to say that poem,
the one that would make
our fears magically go away?
You used to know it by heart.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star...
You remember?
Huh?
Twinkle, twinkle, little star.
How I wonder what you are.
All right?
Up above the world so high.
Like a diamond in the sky.
When the blazing sun is gone,
when he nothing shines upon.
Minx, say the words, honey.
- No.
- Hey, I need you to...
I don't want to do this.
Okay, then you shine your little light
twinkle, twinkle all the night.
Okay?
You're testing me.
Baby, it's just...
I can't... I can't think of
the words right now.
My brain's fuzzy.
Daddy. Daddy, please.
- It's okay.
- Daddy, please.
It's okay.
No.
It's okay, sweetheart.
You don't have to say the words.
You're my dad.
You're supposed to believe me.
Why didn't Minx tell us
she was Drill all along?
- They've me these questions all day.
- Why can't I just go home?
We shared all our secrets together.
I don't know what to tell them.
Drill is just our friend.
I don't know what I did wrong.
Henry?
Are you there?
It's Minx. Can you hear me?
Yeah.
I need your help.
You need to talk to your mom,
tell her I'm not Drill.
Uh, I don't know.
I swear, Henry, I'm not Drill.
You have to help me.
Please.
Do you know what they're gonna do to me?
Aren't you my friend, Henry?
Henry, why aren't you answering me?
They're gonna kill her, Claire.
She's my daughter.
I cannot let that happen.
Wes, that's not Minx.
Even if you're right
and Drill has taken possession of her,
that doesn't mean she's gone.
What if, somewhere inside her
body, my daughter's still alive?
Thomas Harcourt said that when...
Thomas was 8 years old when it happened.
What if he was wrong?
And what if he wasn't?
Wes, we already missed our
chance to end this once before.
Yes, and my wife was killed,
so I am well aware of
the consequences, Claire.
Minx...
Is all I have left.
If I lose her...
So I need you to look at me
and tell me that
you are certain she has gone.
That is not fair.
Look at me in the eye
and tell me she's dead,
that the promise that I made to her when
she was a little girl means nothing
and that there is no hope
that I will ever get her back.
And then...
Then I will believe you.
Sir, we have good news.
We now know which of
the children has been possessed.
Who?
It's Wes Lawrence's daughter.
I know. It's unfortunate.
My daughter, she's...
Perfectly fine.
The other children,
they're... they're all safe.
So we could release them, then.
With all due respect, uh,
we don't know how much influence
he still has over them.
Right now, the most prudent
course of action
is to keep them all locked up
until we know for sure
Drill has been neutralized.
Yes.
I know I made the wrong call, Haley.
Excuse me?
I shouldn't have let him go.
I know that now.
This time, we'll make the right decision.
The questions is, how?
I believe we actually have
the perfect weapon
to accomplish our task.
Three months ago,
I was sent to the Arctic
to test an experimental weapon.
It was an electron-pulse device
designed to emit
an electrical charge equivalent
to 100 lightning strikes.
Unfortunately...
Things didn't go as planned.
We brought him to us.
He saw the energy, and he came right at me.
"He"?
When I saw that blue light...
That was when I knew
that something was here.
"Something"?
Something not human.
I just need more time.
Where are the guards?
Oh, God.
No!
I'm sorry, Wes.
- Where is she?!
- You have to believe me.
I take no solace in what needs to be done.
Sir, you don't have to do this now.
- I just need a few more days, so...
- To what?
T... To remove Drill from her body.
So now you're talking about exorcism?
- Listen to yourself.
- Sir...
No more negotiations, Wes. Please.
We're going to end this today.
No, no. I'm sorry, sir.
- It's best if you weren't here for this.
- Sir, sir.
- Please, you can't... you can't do this.
- Please, escort them out.
You can't do this.
She is an 8-year-old child!
Mr. Secretary, please, give us...
Damn it!
Talking about using this thing on a child?
It's not a child, sir.
It's an alien threat.
Do it. Just get it over with.
I'm not leaving here!
Get off me!
Wes. Wes, Wes, Wes, Wes.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm so sorry.
There has to be another way, Claire.
There has to be another way.
What is that?
That's how they're gonna do it.
That's how they're gonna kill Minx.
We have to do whatever it takes.
We have to save her.
What happens if the president says no?
That's not an option.
- This isn't on you, Claire.
- Isn't it?
You did what you had to do,
just like I did.
What are you talking about?
I just talked to a reporter,
gave him the whole story.
Sean, why would you do that?
Because this exposes everything.
They'll be forced to let our kids go.
That's the only way we get Henry back home.
I have to go.
I'll call you as soon as I can.
I just got off with the press secretary.
Now it's their move.
My contact at the White House,
she's not making any promises,
but she's trying to get us a meeting.
Okay. Let's go.
Mr. President, I'm sorry
for the interruption.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Uh... We got a call from
the Baltimore Observer.
They, uh...
They know about Drill.
How long do we have?
Well, they say about two hours,
but I'm confident I can get
them to hold the story...
That won't be necessary.
Excuse me?
It'll all be over in about two hours.
I want to go live before the story breaks.
Sir, I have to advise against...
Do you understand the kind of
panic that this could cause?
No more than if the leader of this nation
is caught lying to the
very people who elected him.
No more hiding. No more secrets.
This is what must be done.
Yes, sir.
Oh, and, Alan, one more thing.
Get those children home.
I want my daughter back.
Yes, sir.
Where are they taking us?
How should I know?
In a few minutes, we're gonna
go live to the White House,
where President Winters has called
a last-minute press conference.
Please. We don't have much time.
- Okay, I just... I need...
- Wes, I'm...
- I need five minutes with him.
- Wes, I'm trying,
- but now this press conference has come up.
- look, you just...
you just tell him that... that
there's an alternative, okay?
We don't have to pull
the trigger right now.
He'll know what I'm talking about.
- Okay. I'm trying.
- Please.
You don't understand how important this is.
We don't have time.
- Okay.
- Please.
I can't tell you what a relief that is.
I'll be right there. Thank you.
They're letting the kids out.
So it worked.
Looks like Oberon came through.
What's Oberon?
Secret service code name for the president.
Each family member of the family has one.
They all start with the same letter...
first lady, she's Olympia.
And what about the daughter?
Uh, don't know that one
off the top of my head.
Sean.
Orion.
Sean, I can't... I can't talk right now.
Claire, it's Cassandra. She's Drill.
What?
Orion... it's Cassandra's
secret service code name.
What?
You were right.
It isn't Minx.
Copy that. Olympia and Orion on the move.
He's in the White House.
Drill framed Minx.
So Cassandra burned herself.
- Henry?! She must have.
- Minx?
With the evacuation of the children,
there was so much chaos that we...
we weren't looking at her.
We were looking at Minx.
What about Silas? He said he saw Minx.
He was telling the truth about
everything but who he saw.
It was Cassandra who caught him.
She's the one
who threatened to hurt his mom.
What about Maria's computer file?
Cassandra knew that
we'd be able to retrieve it,
so she doctored Minx's file.
Oh, Claire, I...
Go.
Stop them. I'll try
to get to the press room.
Okay.
Honey!
Hey, buddy.
Mommy, daddy, I'm here!
- Henry?
- Dad!
Okay. Come here.
I'm sorry, Mr. Lawrence,
but Secretary Frommer is not available.
Tell him it's not Minx. It's Cassandra.
I can leave word that it's urgent.
Damn it!
Twinkle, twinkle, little star...
How I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high...
Like a diamond in the sky.
When the blazing sun is gone...
When he nothing shines upon...
Then you show your little light.
Twinkle, twinkle...
All the night.
You look nervous.
Well, I suppose I am a little.
Do you remember what you
always tell me when I'm scared?
"Be brave."
All right, well, I will, uh...
I will try to keep that in mind.
Wait, w-what are you...
what are you saying?
The president, he's the target?
But it doesn't make any sense.
If Drill wanted to kill the president,
he could've possessed
Cassandra a long time ago.
Why wait this long?
Press conference.
He's not after the president.
What do you mean?
The broadcast.
Jessup, it's a live feed.
I'm Special Agent Claire Bennigan.
Please, I need you to listen to me.
The press conference...
You have to stop it.
I'm gonna have to ask you to step back.
You don't understand.
This is how he's gonna do it.
My fellow Americans...
To friends watching around the world...
Be brave.
That's what my daughter said
to me before I walked in here.
Such simple words from a child,
but not always easy to do.
Then the traveler in the dark...
Thanks you for your tiny spark...
Mr. Secretary.
I'm sorry, sir. It's... I can't.
Walk me through each step
of the launch sequence.
I'll push the button.
Be brave.
We all do.
'Cause what I am about to tell you
- may be hard to accept.
- Halt!
Halt! Don't move!
Stop! Look out!
We're on him!
For the last few weeks,
our country, our world,
has been battling a secret war
provoked by a silent and deadly enemy,
an enemy unlike any which
we've fought before...
an enemy not from our world.
This being did not come to
our world in peace.
But before we succumb to panic,
I am here to tell you that this war is over
and we have won.
The alien threat has
been captured, contained.
By the time that we are done here,
it will have been destroyed.
Sequence initiated.
Weapon will fire in 60 seconds.
What's the matter, sweetheart?
Weapon will fire in 50 seconds.
I'm ready to see my mommy now.
Weapon will fire in 30 seconds.
Sir!
Sir, it's not Minx! She's not Drill!
What is he doing in here?
Please open the door, sir!
No. No. No. She's gonna do it.
Wes, you do not want to be here.
It's cassandra!
It's the president's daughter!
Sir! Weapon will fire in 15 seconds.
She's gonna send the signal.
10...
- 9...
- Mr. Secretary.
8...7...
There's been an incident at the White House.
- 6...
- Yeah?
- 5...4...
- Oh, my God.
- Stop the countdown.
- ...3...2...
Sequence aborted.
Cassandra?
Is that Drill?
Yeah. It is.
Did he send the signal?
I think so.
What does this mean?
It means we're in trouble.
My angel.
What happened?
Don't worry, Claire.
I'm not going anywhere.
No, daddy.
It's okay.
- Get me out!
- It's okay.
It's okay, baby. It's okay.
Get me out! Okay.
It's all right.
Okay.
It's okay.
Come here.
Here we go. All right, okay.
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay.
All right. Hey. Hey. Hey. Hey.
You're safe now.
I knew you'd come for me, daddy.
Okay.
All right. All right.
It's okay. It's okay.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star.
How I wonder what you are.
Minx?
I was just saying the poem you taught me.
Oh. What?
Did you have another bad dream?
I'm okay. I'm not scared.
Oh. Well, I'm very proud of you.
But just so you know,
if you ever are scared,
if you ever need me,
I promise I'll always be here.
I know, daddy.
There.